ERICA RANCK

MANAGER O F CXSYSTEMS



931,220,1984

✓ ericaranck1@gmail.com



github.com/Erica-Exotica



in linkedin.com/ericaranck

PROFILE

I'm highly organized, process motivated, and I'm most content when I'm analyzing data in Looker or spreadsheets to answer key business questions. I can assist in solving business problems through creating detailed reports, data visualizations, dashboards, and project plans. I'm proficient with Google Sheets/Excel and SQL. I have experience working in a fast-paced, tech-startup environment with an expansive knowledge of the customer service & healthcare industry.

SKILLS

- Looker
- PostgreSQL
- PowerBI
- Tableau
- Python
- Software Administration
- Data Analysis

EDUCATION

DATA ANALYTICS BOOTCAMP

Nashville Software School January -June 2023

GOOGLE DATA ANALYTICS CERTIFICATE

Coursera 2022

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN PSYCHOLOGY

Austin Peay State University 2010-2014

EXPERIENCE

MANAGER OF CX SYSTEMS

Warby Parker

2021 - Present

- Manages data to support process changes and monitor success
- Collaborate with vendors to ensure success of Warby Parker CX
- Implemented Narvar Dynamic Track software and saved \$25k in CX interactions through improved self service
- Realized over \$3 million in ROI across 4 systems

CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE MANAGER

Warby Parker

2017-2021

- Managed a team of highly successful Customer Experience advisors; 2 who went on to become Customer Experience Managers
- Developed spreadsheet organizer that was adopted into CX Manager training which is still apart of the onboarding curriculum
- Oversaw performance metrics and tailored unique plans for success per direct report

COMPREHENSIVE CHILD & FAMILY CASE MANAGER

Mental Health Cooperative 2015-2016

- Promoted from general case manager to Comprehensive Child & Family Case Manager within 5 months
- Provided local resources for housing, food, and income assistance
- Responded to urgent/crisis situation with appropriate protocol per crisis plan developed by case manager and client